We are continuously bombarded by
私たちは常に光子によって
light, photons.
光、つまり光子によって絶えず bombardé されています。
And what's quite incredible is that a part of your brain, which is the retina,
そして、驚くべきことに、あなたの脳の一部である網膜は、
is capable of contacting the smallest
最も小さな光の粒子、
possible particle of light, that is, a photon.
つまり光子と接触することができます。
The eye, we will see that it has a very great activity at the level of...
目は、非常に大きな活動を...
cerebral, that it is even an exteriorized brain, it is an expansion
脳レベルで行っており、それは外在化した脳であり、あなたの脳の拡張であるとわかるでしょう。
of your brain.
あなたの脳の拡張です。
And we will see that this eye will naturally have an importance at the level of the static of
そして、この目は、あなたの首の静力学において自然に重要であることを理解するでしょう。それはあなたの重心に直接影響を与えます。
your neck, it will therefore directly influence your center of gravity.
あなたの首の静力学において自然に重要であることを理解するでしょう。それはあなたの重心に直接影響を与えます。
And so the eye, at the same time it influences your center of gravity, and at the same time your
したがって、目はあなたの重心に影響を与え、同時にあなたの
center
重心が
of gravity influences the eye. So the eye is in fact the lighthouse of all the facials. Ocular tensions, which we see in our consultations, are often related to the liver.
目に影響を与えます。
to the liver.
肝臓と関連しています。
Whether it's a red eye or a yellow eye,
目が赤いか黄色いかにかかわらず、
they are a hepatic expression.
それらは肝臓の表現です。
The heart too, there is an important thing,
心臓もまた、重要なことがあります。
it is that already in embryology,
それは、すでに発生学において、
the eye will come to rest
目が心臓の上に
on the heart.
置かれるということです。
And it will receive
そして、それは
a rhythmic information,
リズミカルな情報を受け取ります。
like the throat, that is to say
喉、つまりあなたの声、そして
your voice, and like
手のように。すでに、
the hands. Already, the information
あなたの手の情報、
of your hands, the information
あなたの目の情報、
of your eyes, the information
あなたの声の情報は、
of your voice are already
すでに電気的、
electrical charges,
磁気的、
magnetic,
電磁気的な
electromagnetic.
電荷です。
You work
あなたは
you work with your eyes.
目を使って仕事をします。
We can
私たちは
hypnotize someone, you see,
誰かを催眠術にかけることができます。
by voice. Be careful,
声で。注意してください。
I'm talking.
私は自分自身に話しかけます。
these frequencies in fact because they are electric fields so same thing with your hands, same
これらの周波数は、実際には電場なので、手でも同じです。
thing with the eyes. But in fact what happens is that we modify
目でも同じです。しかし、実際には何が起こっているかというと、私たちは
alpha frequencies,
アルファ波の周波数を変えています。
you see all these brain frequencies which are also important phenomena of stabilization,
これらの脳波はすべて、安定化のための重要な現象でもあります。
but in fact the eye already receives information from the heart, from the primary
しかし、実際には、目はすでに心臓からの情報を受け取っています。
heart, from the good heart. Buddhists
原初の心臓、良い心臓から。仏教徒は
They say there is a small invisible thread that connects the heart and
心臓と目をつなぐ目に見えない細い糸があると言います。
the eyes.
目。
Do this exercise of looking at me with your heart.
心で私を見るというこの練習をしてください。
Really make that connection.
本当にこのつながりを作るように。
To change and look at me like that.
変えて、このように私を見てください。
And you will see that something will change in the eye.
そうすれば、目に何かが変わるのがわかるでしょう。
There is a geometry.
そこには幾何学があります。
The geometry of the smile.
笑顔の幾何学。
These are very subtle geometric changes.
これらは非常に微妙な幾何学的変化です。
to look with the heart.
心で見ること。
Because a word, a gesture, a look
なぜなら、言葉、ジェスチャー、視線は
blocks someone for a lifetime.
誰かを一生ブロックするからです。
But a word, a gesture, a look,
しかし、言葉、ジェスチャー、視線は、
if it is placed at the right time,
もしそれが適切なタイミングで、
the right space,
適切な空間で、
with the right mental image,
適切な心のイメージとともに置かれれば、
can free someone.
誰かを解放することができます。
But for that, you need to have the right timing.
しかし、そのためには適切なタイミングが必要です。
Here, we want to be recognized,
私たちは認められたいと思っています。
to be able to emerge from that.
そこから抜け出すために。
Same thing with your hands, and same thing with your voice.
手でも同じです。声でも同じです。
This is about attention, because if we want to work on vision,
これは注意です。なぜなら、視力を鍛えたいなら、
we must learn to be attentive.
注意深くなることを学ばなければならないからです。
So attention is a tool that we must sharpen.
したがって、注意は磨くべきツールです。
The kidneys will modify your vision, your perception of reality, through fear.
腎臓は、恐怖によってあなたの視覚、あなたの現実の認識を変化させます。
reality.
現実。
Fear can completely change it.
恐怖はそれを完全に変えることができます。
We lose like anger, you see, boom, I change my reality.
怒りのように、ほら、私は現実を変える。
Initially, anger is a force of clairvoyance.
もともと、怒りは透視の力です。
But at the moment when anger arises, if you are attentive,
しかし、怒りが湧き上がったとき、注意していれば、
there is a clarity.
そこには明晰さがあります。
We see the fault.
私たちは間違いを見ます。
The work will be an embryology work, an anatomy work,
この研究は、発生学の研究であり、解剖学の研究であり、
a work of functional studies and then a slightly more spiritual work on the eye.
機能研究であり、そして目に関するもう少し精神的な研究でもあります。
So we're going to work a little bit on what we call the differences.
そこで、私たちは「違い」と呼ばれるものを少し研究します。
which are important because it will give us what we call the world of perception,
それは重要です。なぜなら、それは私たちに「知覚の世界」を与えるからです。
the world of sensation, the world of volition, the world of consciousness.
感覚の世界、意志の世界、意識の世界です。
But learning to be able to gradually distinguish between perhaps
しかし、少しずつ、現れるかもしれない幻想との区別をつけられるようになることを学ぶ必要があります。
the illusion that may appear there.
それは簡単ではありません。なぜなら、私たちはすぐに「偏見」と呼ばれるものを持ってしまうからです。
So there, he is confident.
だから、彼は自信を持っています。
That means he will undergo his environment, the totality of his environment.
それは、彼が自分の環境、その環境全体に影響されることを意味します。
And in fact, it is there before the bone.
そして実際、それは骨の前に存在します。
So it will be the soft that will control the hard. It will have laws, laws of position, laws of mobility, laws of information integration. And then, we will also have to understand this purely neurosensory level of the eye, this pathway of neuromotor involvement that we will study, because we will still study neurophysiology.
したがって、柔らかいものが硬いものを制御することになります。
this pathway of neuromotor involvement that we will study, because we will still study neurophysiology.
私たちが研究するこの神経運動の関与の経路は、神経生理学も研究するからです。
We will still go into a little detail from the moment we touch
私たちは、目に触れる瞬間から、もう少し詳しく見ていきます。
the eye,
目、
where a photon will touch the eye, everything that will happen.
光子が目に触れると、何が起こるか。
From your conjunctiva, your cornea, all these liquids that it will touch, boom,
結膜、角膜、触れるすべての液体から、タック、
and it will at some point perform a transduction.
そして、ある時点で変換が起こります。
So it will change this light into electricity.
つまり、この光を電気に変えるのです。
And then it will go into the lateral geniculate body.
そして、それは外側膝状体に向かいます。
So it will go into a part of your brain.
つまり、それはあなたの脳の一部に向かいます。
which will be completely influenced in the whole system of papillae,
それは、パペットのシステム全体に完全に影響されます。
we will see, and then with the olivary nuclei, the pulvinar, all that will be integrated,
私たちは、オリーブ核、プルビナーなど、すべてが統合されるのを見るでしょう。
to go towards a radiation on the occipital areas,
後頭葉の放射に向かって、
which will transmit another information to us,
それは私たちに別の情報を伝達します。
that is to say that we lose 80% of reality.
つまり、私たちは現実の80%を失っているということです。
Already in our way of seeing, that's crazy,
すでに私たちの見方において、これは狂っています。
that is to say that we are very strongly influenced by our experience.
つまり、私たちは自分の経験に非常に強く影響されているということです。
We will lose 80%.
私たちは80%を失います。
It's almost organized.
それはほとんど組織化されています。
We will always be in a mechanism of interpretation.
私たちは常に解釈のメカニズムの中にいます。
And as soon as there is emotion, as soon as there are stories that are lived, we will see things again
そして、感情があるとき、経験された物語があるとき、私たちは物事をそのように見直します。
like that.
そのように。
And so it will be important little by little to dare to be curious.
だから、少しずつ好奇心を持つことを恐れないことが重要です。
And so the goal as an osteopath will be to be able to receive this information,
したがって、オステオパシー医としての目的は、これらの情報を受け取ることです。
of environmental type too, because we will not only look at one thing,
環境的なものも、なぜなら私たちは一つのことだけを見るわけではないからです。
one thing,
一つのこと、
but also this facial level.
しかし、この顔のレベルもです。
So treating the eye is treating the whole body.
つまり、目を治療することは全身を治療することです。
But to treat the eye, you must first treat the whole body.
しかし、目を治療するためには、まず全身を治療しなければなりません。
We can say that the eye is like a kind of balance
目はある種のバランスのようなものだと言えます。
between a structure in which it is integrated
それが統合された構造と
and the problem that can be expressed.
現れる可能性のある問題との間の。
So it will be a balance.
だから、それはバランスになるでしょう。